A Guide to the Records of the Office of Academic Affairs, 1961-1977 (bulk 1965-1976)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series VIII: Records and Correspondence, 1970-1971
  - Leaves and Leave Policy, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Letters - Students, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Library Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Automated Library System Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Library, Branch Libraries (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Library Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
  - Living-Learning Committee Minutes, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Loans, Grants, and Scholarships, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mathematics - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Mechanical Engineering Report of Annual Faculty Workload, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Media Center-Learning Resource Center, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Microwave Length, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Motor Pool Vehicles, Use of, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (2 folders), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - NASULGC - Council on Academic Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
  - "News Reports", 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Off Campus Courses, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Off Campus Instruction, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, Department of, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Policies, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Philippines Trip by Dr. Malpass, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Includes space planning standards
  - Physics Department, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Placement, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Plant Pathology and Physiology, Department of, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Political Science, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - President's Staff Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Proposals - Safety STS, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Purchase of Books and Periodicals with Departmental Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Psychology Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations, Letters of, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations, Letters of, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Records Administration Program and Transfer Listing, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Regional Education and Laboratory for Carolina and Virginia - Minutes, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Regional Science Association Newsletters, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Regional Studies, Review of, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Registrar, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Research Division - Correspondence and Minutes (4 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 15-18)
    - Bulletins of manual for proposal presentation
  - Research Support Services, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Resident Colleges, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Resumes of Books, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Retirement - Local, 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Retirement - TIAA - CREF, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Roles and Responsibilities of Department Heads, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - ROTC Program Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Scanning Scope Spring, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships Information, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Scholarships and Grants, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Rhodes Scholarship
  - Science Development Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Showalter Memorial Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Sociology Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) - Summer Intern Program, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Special Academic Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Sporn Award, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Staff Meetings (Administrative), 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Statistics Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs (3 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
    - Gay alliance
    - SGA
    - ABC policies
    - Student life policies
    - Student health
  - Student Budgets, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Student budget
    - Student Union
  - Student Government Association (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
  - Student Personnel Division (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence
  - Students, Meetings with, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Study Abroad - Austria, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Study Abroad - Darton/Evans Trip to Europe, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Study Abroad - General, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Study Abroad - General, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Study Abroad - Great Britain, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Study Abroad - Letters, Registrar, Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Study Abroad - Netherlands, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Study Abroad Program, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Study Abroad, Virginia Council for, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Teaching Innovations Group, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Teaching-Learning Grants and Proposals (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
  - Teaching-Learning Grants Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Teaching-Learning Grant Reports - Dr. Darnton (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Television Study Group, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Terminations - Administrative Problems (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
    - Campus unrest
  - United Fund Drive, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - University Allocations, Promotions, and Propositions, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - University Committees - Nominations and Elections, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - University Council Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - University Forms, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - University Traffic Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - University Professors' Nominations, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Veterinary Science Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Vice President - Finance, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Awards presented at the 30th annual meeting
  - Visiting Professors, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Visiting Scholar, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Vice President - Academic Affairs (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Vice President - Student Affairs Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Water Resources Research Center, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Work-Study Program, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Wine Awards, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - YMCA, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - YMCA - Dr. Darton, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Series IX: Records and Correspondence, 1971-1972
  - Academic Administrative Intern Program (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
  - Accounting, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Admissions Office Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Aerospace Engineering- Report of Annual Faculty Workload, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
  - Army Research Office in Durham, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Association, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Biafran Book Fund, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Biology, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Biochemistry, Department of, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Biological Control Center, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Board of Visitors, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Boys' State, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Budget Information, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Unusual equipment needs, classified personnel, grant monies, etc.
  - Catalog Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - CEC, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Center for Economic Education, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Chemistry Department, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Choral Music Organization, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Agriculture, College of - Correspondence (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 31-32)
  - Agriculture, College of - Space, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Agriculture and Life Sciences, College of - A Research Program for the 70's, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Architecture, College of - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Arts and Sciences (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Business (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Education, College of (4 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5-8)
  - Engineering, College of (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Engineering - Aerospace, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, College of - Charles Beasley (2 folders), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
    - "Strip Mining and Coal"
  - Engineering - Chemical Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Engineering - Civil Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Engineering - Electrical Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Engineering - Engineering Consulting, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Engineering - Engineering Curricula, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Engineering - Engineering Science and Mechanics, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Engineering - Industrial Engineering and Operations Research, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Engineering - Mechanical Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Engineering - Mining Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Home Economics, College of Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Evaluation, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Commission on Research - Graduate Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (6 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 28-30, Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee on Employee Benefits, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, Meetings of - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Computer Science Department, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Computerized Management Network: User Guide (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Fraternities (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Sororities, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Constitutions and By-Laws - Student Organizations, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Deans Council Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Deans' Memos, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Deans, Meetings with Dr. Malpass, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Dairy Science and Entomology, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Educational Research and Needs of the Roanoke Valley and Southwest Virginia, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - English Department General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Extension Division (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
  - Extension Division - General Correspondence (3 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 20-22)
  - Extension - Consulting Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Extension - Task Force, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Executive Vice President, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Leaving this Year, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Senate, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Wage Price Freeze, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Work Load Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Five-Year Plans: Priorities, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Ford Foundation, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Foreign Languages, History and Math, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Division of Forestry and Wildlife Sciences (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 34, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Freshman and Transfer Student Profiles, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Gay Alliance, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - GE Incentive Awards, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Geology Department, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - GTA Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Gulf Oil Real Estate Development Company, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Industry Center, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - International Program, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Learning Resources Center - Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Learning Resources Center - Agreements and Contacts, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Learning Resources Center - Candidate File, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Learning Resources Center - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Learning Resources Center - Educational TV Cable System, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Leave Education, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Libraries Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Library Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - NASULGC Council on Academic Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Office of the President - Correspondence (4 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 25-28)
  - President's Staff Meeting - Agenda and Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Performing Arts and Communications, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Philippines Program, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Philosophy and Religion, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Physics Department, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Physics: Ijaz, M.A., 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Planetarium, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Political Science, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Position Applications, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Promotion and Tenure Material, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Psychology, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Psychology - Search Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Purchase of Equipment, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Reconciliation Committee, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Research (3 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
  - Research - Developmental Goals and Priorities for the College of Education, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Five-Year Plan for Research (3 folders), 1971 (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
  - Senate Counsel, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Statistics Department, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Terminal Interview Report, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Study Abroad, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Teacher Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Terminal Interview Data, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Travel, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - University Traffic Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Upward Bound - Summer Program Evaluation, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Urban Interdisciplinary Study Council - Dyck, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Veterinary Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs - Correspondence (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 27-28)
  - Vice President of Finance - Correspondence (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 29-30)
  - Travel, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - VPA, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence - Water Resources Center, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Weighted Student Credit Hours, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Women's Status, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - WUVT, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Series X: Records and Correspondence, 1972-1973
  - Subseries A: College of Agriculture, 1972-1973
    - Agricultural Economics Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture Faculty Association, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture Programs, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture Research, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Agronomy Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Anaerobe Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Animal Science, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Biochemistry and Nutrition, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture Consulting Activities (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
    - Dairy Science Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Department Evaluation, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Entomology Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Food Science and Technology Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Forestry and Wildlife Resources, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Horticulture Department, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Veterinary Science, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Subseries B: College of Architecture, 1972-1973
    - Administrative and Divisional Revision, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Budget and Finances, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Consulting, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Curriculum, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - New Franconia Proposal, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Off Campus Experimental Program, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Reston Project, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Wood Research and Construction, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Subseries C: College of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973
    - Biology Department (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 36-37)
    - Chemistry Department, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Computer Science, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Consulting (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 40, Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum General, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - English Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Activity (General), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Candidates (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
    - Foreign Language Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Geology Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - History Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Mathematics, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - New Marching Virginians, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Performing Arts and Communications, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Philosophy and Religion, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Physics, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Political Science Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Psychology Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - ROTC (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
    - Sociology Department, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Subseries D: College of Business, 1972-1973
    - Accounting Department (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 22-23)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Business Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Consulting, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Economics Department (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 27-28)
    - Faculty Activity, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - MBA Program, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Students, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Subseries E: College of Education, 1972-1973
    - Administrative and Educational Services, 1970-1973 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Accreditation and Awards, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Education Conference, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Developmental Goals and Priorities for the College of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Federal City College, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Consulting, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum and Instruction (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
    - Elementary Education Program, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - HPER, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Vocational and Technical, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Year Abroad Program, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Subseries F: College of Engineering, 1972-1973
    - Engineering (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 16-18)
    - Aerospace Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Bachelor's of Engineering Technology Proposal, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Civil Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Consulting, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Engineering Extension, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Engineering Fundamentals, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Engineering Science and Mechanics, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Industrial Engineering and Operations Research, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Mining Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Subseries G: College of Home Economics, 1972-1973
    - Home Economics, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Consulting, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Space Needs, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Gerontology Program, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Human Nutrition and Foods Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Subseries H: Graduate School, 1972-1973
    - Graduate School (4 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 37, Box 33, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries I: Extension, 1972-1973
    - Extension (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
    - 4-H Extension, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Extension - Consulting Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Extension - Donaldson Brown Center for Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Subseries J: Commissions, 1972-1973
    - Commission on Faculty Affairs - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies (4 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 11-14)
    - Commission on Student Affairs (4 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 15-18)
    - Commission on Student Affairs - Constitutions of Various Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Student Affairs - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Student Affairs - Residence Hall Federation, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 22-23)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies - Academic Appeals Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Subseries K: General Correspondence, Reports, and Papers, A-Z, 1972-1973
    - Academic Correspondence, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Academic Drops, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The Academic Register, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Accounting Office, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Adjunct Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Interns, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Admissions (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - Admissions Registrar - Academic Drops, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)